东西在吗
Do you have them?
谢谢
Thank you.
人生切割术
第二季 第五集
- 嘿 - 嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
周末那个活动怎么样
How was the weekend thing?
挺好吧
Good, I guess.
不过据说我公司里的自己 从绳索上掉下来了
Although my innie fell off a rope, apparently.
绳索
A rope?
你受伤了吗
Are you hurt?
没有 就只是弄湿了
No, I just got a little wet, that's all.
天 这些人真的不消停
Jesus, it's like it never ends with these guys.
你知道到底发生了什么吗
Do you know what the fuck actually happened?
我不知道
I have no idea.
要命 你那个 “烧眼球传信”计划怎么样了
Fuck. Well, how's the old "burning shit into your eyeballs" thing going?
我没法延长到足够的时间
I still can't get it to last long enough.
这样啊 那我们怎么办
Okay. So, what do we do?
只能继续尝试了
Just keep trying, I guess.
你有其他主意吗
Do you have any other ideas?
嘿 抱歉 我得去上班了
Hey, I'm sorry. I gotta get to work.
- 好 拜拜 - 是 拜拜
- All right. Bye. - Yeah. Bye.
- 嘿 - 你的烘干机该修了
- Hey. - You need to get your dryer fixed.
是 或者其实你该换个地方住
Yeah. Or you could just, like, not live here.
我不能总是进进出出的
I can't keep coming in and out.
你觉得他们在监视
You think they're watching us?
取决于你装傻装得多像
Depends on how dumb you've played it.
嘿 我们什么时候继续
Hey, when do we keep going?
今晚吧 我晚点决定
Maybe tonight. I'll decide later.
因为我还没记起任何其他事
'Cause I haven't remembered anything else.
是 也许你公司里的自己记起来了
Right. Well, maybe your innie has.
你周末剩下的时间都用来休息恢复了
You took the rest of the weekend to recover?
我没事
I'm fine.
我之后要给父亲报告最新进展吗
Will I be updating Father later?
应该由我直接向他报告
He should hear it from me.
我们已决定不让他得知这次的挫折
We have decided to spare him knowledge of this contretemps.
那请告诉他 他的女儿还活着 安然无恙
Well, please let him know that his daughter is alive and well.
医疗人员说 你的脾气很快将恢复平衡
The medical team says your tempers will rebalance quickly.
那就好
Good to hear.
经历了这样的折磨 一定是有一些遗留的创伤
Some residual trauma is to be expected after such an ordeal.
也许我们今天傍晚可以再安排一个义务会
Perhaps we could arrange another obligement session this evening.
我说了我没事
I said I'm fine.
我们很接近目标了 海伦娜
We're close, Helena.
他目前达到多少了 78%
What's he at, 78%?
81% 截至周五
Eighty-one. As of Friday.
不用很久了
It won't be much longer.
你能做到的
You can do this.
我不会回到地下了
I'm not going back down there.
不是“你” 是你公司里的自己
It won't be you. It will be your innie.
那个曾想杀了我的“公司里的自己”
My innie who tried to kill me?
还有另一个人也想杀了我
And then the other one tried to kill me.
他们是一群禽兽
They're fucking animals.
我只要继续伪装就好了
I'll just fake it again.
我们不能冒这个险
We can't take that chance.
我们必须纠正这个局面
We need to clean this up.
米尔奇克这周末多次犯错 迫使我们这么做
Milchick's many errors this weekend have forced our hand.
父亲也批准了吗
And Father approves?
父亲支持这么做
Father encouraged it.
这有风险
It's a risk.
我们明白
We know this.
但没有别的解决方法了
But there is no other solution.
她不在 马克S就不愿工作
Mark S. won't work without her.
而他的工作神秘且重要
And the work is mysterious and important.
所以我们必须把她给他
So we must give him her.
董事会感谢你的牺牲
The Board appreciates your sacrifice.
早安 赫莉R
Good morning, Helly R.
你是谁
Who the fuck are you?
我是黄小姐
I'm Miss Huang.
搞什么
What the hell?
请跟我来
Please follow me.
米尔奇克先生将为你解释
Mr. Milchick will explain.
- 嗨 - 嗨
- Hey. - Hey.
- 她是... - 她公司里的自己
- Is she... - Her innie.
宏观数据精检
MDR.
再次大团圆
Together again.
请进
Come on in.
我必须知道发生了什么
I need to know what's going on.
现在
Like, right now.
欧文在哪
Where's Irving?
他为什么想淹死我
And why was he trying to drown me?
因为你是该死的伊根家的人
'Cause you're a fucking Eagan.
- 她在监视我们吗  - 等等 什么
- Was she spying on us? - Wait, what?
一直都在
The whole time.
这叫格拉斯哥屏障
It's called a Glasgow block.
- 它允许外面的自己... - 等一等
- It allows one's outie to-- - Wait.
你是说她曾来过地下
Are you saying that she was down here?
冒充我
As me?
也许她此刻就在地下呢
Maybe she still is.
嘿 我再问一次 欧文在哪
Hey, I repeat myself. Where is Irving?
- 对啊 他人呢  - 我完全糊涂了
- Yeah, where is he? - I'm so confused.
回答我的问题
Answer my question!
不好意思
Excuse me.
海伦娜伊根作为高管 此前在进行宝贵的研究工作
Helena Eagan, in her executive capacity, was conducting valuable research.
通过偷走我的身体
By stealing my fucking body?
欧文不知道管理层如此做的意图是什么
Irving had no knowledge of what management's intention was in this action,
因此 他几乎把你淹死
and in so doing, he nearly drowned you.
我们唯一的选择是对他永久免职
Our only option was permanent dismissal.
所以 他死了
So he is dead?
不
No.
欧文B外面的自己已踏上长期的邮轮之旅
Irving B's outie has departed on an elongated cruise voyage.
我才不在乎他外面的自己
I don't give three dry fucks about his outie.
她没有权利夺走我的身份
She doesn't have the right to take my identity.
你们听过格拉虚潘的故事吗
Have you ever heard the story of the Gråkappan?
你就当作我们都没听过吧
Let's assume we haven't.
在远古时代 瑞典国王本人
In ancient times, the king of Sweden himself
出了名地爱微服私访
was known to go incognito amongst his people
希望借此了解百姓真实的忧虑
in the hopes of learning their true grievances.
他会穿着老旧 灰色的 叫“格拉虚潘”的袍子
He would don an old, gray robe, a Gråkappan,
他也因此被后世称为格拉虚潘国王
the name for which he was remembered,
用来伪装王室身份
to disguise his royal vestments.
基尔伊根在世时也会 伪装成百姓 去他的乙醚工厂
Kier Eagan himself was known to do so in his ether factories,
伊根女士则沿袭了这一高贵的传统
and Ms. Eagan was carrying on this noble tradition.
感觉像是一派胡言
This smells like horseshit.
对 用瑞典语说的一派胡言 而且欧文就是死了
Yeah. Swedish horseshit, and Irving is still dead.
正如我说 欧文外面的自己已踏上长期...
As I said, Irving B's outie has departed on an elonga--
踏上了长期的邮轮之旅 我知道
On an elongated cruise voyage. Yeah, I know.
他到底会不会回来
Is he gonna come back or not?
不会了
He is not.
天啊 总算说了句真话
Wow. Some actual honesty.
你们是杀人犯
You fucking murderers.
你们不能这样对人
You can't do this to people.
要消化发生的一切需要时间
It will take time to absorb all that has occurred.
聊得很顺利
This went well.
请允许我送你们去宏观数据精检部
Allow me to escort you to MDR
帮助你们重新熟悉工作环境
and help reacclimate you to your work environment.
搞什么
What in the abominable fuck?
这是你的工位
This is you.
绝对不要 我不会靠近那地方
Hell no. I'm not going near that thing.
迪伦 拜托
Dylan, please.
如果你需要意见反馈 我的意见是 我讨厌它
If you're taking feedback, I hate it.
我也是
Same.
户外团建对所有人来说都是个挑战 无论是预期中还是预期外的
Well, the ORTBO was a challenge for us all in ways expected and non.
比如杰姆伊根的女儿给我们来了个 “格拉虚潘微服私访”
You mean like Jame Eagan's daughter Gråkappanning us?
请注意言辞 迪伦 言语是有后果的
Careful, Dylan. Words have consequences.
我不希望撤销某些优待权利
I'd hate to rescind certain privileges.
正如你们所见 你们的所有物品
As you can see, all of your items
都已搬到新的三向工位
have been moved to your new work tri-stations.
你们仍会获得通行证
Hall passes will still be available.
让我们举办葬礼吧
Let us have a funeral.
不好意思 什么
I'm sorry?
欧文是一个人 他不在了
Irving is a person, and he's gone.
所以
So,
我们想办个葬礼
we'd like to have a funeral.
不是退休派对 而是葬礼
Not a retirement party, a funeral.
对吗
Right?
是
Yeah.
葬礼
A funeral.
这是宏观数据精检部的诉求
Is this MDR's position?
哥们
Dude?
帮帮忙啊
Little help?
当然 只要时间短点就可以
Sure. As long as it's quick.
- 短点  - 短点 对
- Quick? - Quick. Yes.
那就不用耗去一整天时间
So it doesn't take up the whole day.
说得很好 马克
Well said, Mark.
我会研究一下怎么办的
I'll see if we can pull something together.
在那之前 请各位推进一下 手头文件的进度
In the meantime, let's make some forward progress on the files at hand.
好吗
Shall we?
谢谢
Thank you.
不是对你说
Not you.
黄小姐 我们需要为宏观数据精检 准备哀悼用具
Miss Huang, we need to ready a bereavement kit for MDR.
我们去后勤办公室见
Meet me in the back office.
马克
Mark?
在吗
Hello?
我进来了
I'm gonna come in.
I'm coming in.
嘿
Hey.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
嗯哼 不太好
Uh-huh. No, not really.
是 整件事太荒谬了
Yeah. This is seriously fucked up.
是啊
Yeah.
你没看出来
You couldn't tell?
她不是我
That she wasn't me?
显然没有
Obviously not.
她人是什么样的
What was she like?
和你一样
Like you.
或者应该说你和她一样 不知道
Or you're like her? I don't know.
看来我并不了解你是谁
I don't know who you are, I guess.
你了解的
Yes, you do.
好吧
Okay.
我外面的自己 劫持了我的身体 这不是我的错
It's not my fault that my outie hijacked me.
是 当然不是 我懂的 那么做太糟了
Yeah. No, totally. I get it. It sucks.
- 马克 - 是
- Mark... - Yeah.
你在地上遭遇了什么
What happened to you up there?
那不重要
Doesn't matter.
- 不重要  - 对
- It doesn't matter? - No.
你不想知道我遭遇了什么吗
Don't you want to hear what happened to me?
我不想 我们尽量忘了那些吧 好吗
No, I don't. And let's just try to forget it. Okay?
(卢蒙)
我以为只会为在楼里 死去的公司里的自己举办哀悼活动
I thought bereavement events were for innies who die on the floor.
没错
Yes.
对欧文B的喜爱指数近70分
Well, the Affections Index for Irving B. was in the high 60s.
这能帮助其他员工处理哀悼情绪
It will help the others to grieve.
我可以问个问题吗
May I say a question?
可以
You may.
你不应该允许他们举办葬礼
You shouldn't let them have a funeral.
那会让他们感到自己是一个人
It makes them feel like people.
这不是个问题
That wasn't a question.
而是你的意见
That was an opinion.
而且我没有征询你的意见
Unsolicited.
你的第一次表现评核是在今天 对吗
Your first performance review is today, right?
这是个问题
That was a question.
我会准备茶点
I'll ready the refreshments.
你专心印悼念标语就好
You focus on the mournful signage.
(卢蒙)
今天 我们在此纪念欧文B
Today we honor Irving B.
(欧文B 第870季度至第882季度)
通常 当一位公司里的自己去基尔身边时
Normally, when an innie goes to be with Kier,
我们会举办退休派对 他们本人会出席
we hold a retirement party, which they attend.
但考虑到令我们聚集在这里的 突然而令人心寒的事件
But given the sudden and frigid events which brought us here,
举办退休派对不可行
that's not feasible.
因此 让我们各自用九秒的时间
As such, let us each take nine seconds
默默铭记欧文 并感谢基尔让我们有幸与他共事
to silently remember Irving and thank Kier for our time with him.
好了 可以抬起头 睁开眼睛了
There. You may now lift your heads and open your eyes.
接下来 迪伦G将为我们发表悼词
We will now have a eulogy from Dylan G.
要挑选我最爱的欧文回忆很难
It's hard to pinpoint a favorite Irving story.
作为一个非常无趣的人 他其实很有趣
For the least fun guy in the world, he was really fun.
他在起矛盾时 就是个混蛋
He put the "dick" in contradiction.
有一次 他气我给墨盒兑水
One time, he was pissed at me for watering down the toner,
所以他把碳粉放进我的水杯
so he put toner in my water cup.
不过他没让我把水真喝下去
He stopped me before I drank it, though.
他只是想表明自己的态度 而不是真的伤害我的身体
He just wanted to make a point, not harm me physically.
可我后来不小心喝了一口 因为我忘了他的话
But I did accidentally take a sip of it later 'cause I forgot he said that.
在结束前的不久 他让我帮他做一件事 我没听
He asked me for help with something near the end, and I didn't listen.
在临终前
And in his final moments,
他完全有理由跟我说“滚一边去”
he would have been totally justified in telling me to suck my own fuck.
但他没有那么做
But he didn't.
对
Yeah.
他是个很棒的人 我很想他
He was awesome, and I miss him.
谢谢你 迪伦G
Thank you, Dylan G.
你一如既往的辛辣风格里掺了一点糖
A little sugar with your usual salt.
谢谢各位的出席和参与
Thank you for your attendance and your participation.
你们可以尝一尝欧文的水果头
You may now briefly partake in Irving's fruit head,
深色的头发是黑美人西瓜的皮
whose dark hair is courtesy of the Black Beauty Watermelon.
产自马来西亚
From the country of Malaysia.
黄小姐
Miss Huang.
(无恶意殿)
我以为我要表演的
I thought I was going to perform.
是 我感觉泰勒明音乐还是适度比较好
Yes, well, I feel the theremin works best in moderation.
- 但我练了... - 你可以之后再为我演奏
- But I practiced-- - You can play your piece for me later.
是吧
Yes?
(坚持就是胜利)
你还好吧
You okay?
你呢
How about you?
还好
Okay.
你不留下吗
You're not staying?
我得去工作了 不过今天的仪式很棒 各位
I gotta get to work, but great ceremony, guys.
你认真的
Seriously?
其实 已经算是结束了吧
I mean, isn't it kind of over?
马克
Mark...
让他去吧
Just let him go.
- 什么  - 欧文是你的朋友 他已经死了
- What? - Irving was your friend, and he's dead.
- 你怎么都不在乎  - 因为他没死
- Why don't you give a shit? - Because he's not dead.
他只是不在这里了
He's just not here.
你们叙旧了
You two catch up?
什么
What's that?
你告诉她凯西女士是你妻子了没
You tell her Ms. Casey's your wife yet?
等等 什么
Wait, what?
对 她是我外面的自己的妻子 但是 没错...
Yeah, I mean, it's my outie's wife, but sure...
不 是很疯狂
No, it's pretty crazy.
马克
Mark.
马克 什么鬼
Mark, what the hell?
- 你为什么不和我聊  - 赫莉 你想聊什么
- Why won't you talk to me? - What do you want to talk about, Helly?
不知道呢 也许聊聊 凯西女士是你外面自己的妻子
I don't know. Maybe the fact that Ms. Casey's your outie's wife?
我们能做什么
What are we gonna do?
我们什么都不做
Well, we're not gonna do anything.
什么都不做
Not gonna do anything?
- 真的  - 对 真的
- Seriously? - Yes. Seriously.
别这样 我们一起努力 我们会想到办法
Come on. We'll work as a team. We'll figure this out.
- “我们” 不存在“我们” 赫莉 - 什么
- "We'll"? There's no "we," Helly. - What?
- 不重要了 - 为什么
- It doesn't matter. - Why?
- 为什么  - 对啊
- Why? - Yeah. Why?
因为他们比我们聪明 好吗
Because they are smarter than us, okay?
他们无所不知
They know everything.
我找凯西女士
Me looking for Ms. Casey,
我们四处逛 见其他部门的人
us wandering around, meeting other departments,
画楼层的地图 他们都知道
mapping the floor, all of it.
他们知道我们在做的一切
They know everything we're doing
因为海伦娜把我们做的一切都告诉了他们
because Helena told them everything we're doing.
那不是我
That wasn't me.
马克 听...我不是她 我不是
Mark, lo... I'm not her. I'm not.
我是我
I'm me.
赫莉
Helly.
我要怎么确定
And how do I know that?
你无法确定
You don't.
你只能信任我
You just have to trust me.
你我之间是真的
This is real.
这里并非一切都是谎言
Not everything here is a lie.
你也别再这么混账了
And stop being a fucking asshole.
你担任部门主管后的第一次 表现评核 感到激动吗
Your first performance review as Department Chief. Excited?
非常激动
Very much so.
开始吧
Shall we?
娜塔莉 在开始之前
Natalie, just before we begin,
能不能先和你说几句话
I was wondering if I could have a word with you.
那些画
The paintings.
我希望你明白我很感激
I want you to understand I am grateful for them.
真心的
Truly.
如果画作是对我的一种认可 那么我接受这份认可
If they're a measure of appreciation, then I accept that appreciation.
我只是好奇 你能否与我分享一下
I was just wondering if you could share with me a little
你收到那些画时的感受
how you felt when you received the paintings.
因为我觉得
Because I'm thinking
我们在公司的经历有一些相似之处
our experiences here have been similar in some ways,
我们面临类似的挑战
we face similar challenges,
画作和它们给我们激起的 复杂情感也许也是类似的
and perhaps the paintings and the somewhat complicated feelings they evoke.
达蒙德先生在等候
Mr. Drummond's waiting.
是 好的
Yes, of course.
我们走吧
Let us go.
好吧 混蛋
Okay, asshole.
看来该道别了
Guess this is it.
抱歉 我让你失望了
Sorry I let you down.
(从自光学与设计部走 先向右转 走到头)
(再向右转 一直走到 一条长长的走廊另一端)
欢迎 米尔奇克先生
Welcome, Mr. Milchick.
(表现评核手册)
今天 我将主持你的月度表现评核
Today, I will be conducting your monthly performance review.
这次评核可能要用两至六个小时
This review can take anywhere from two to six hours,
取决于所需的忏悔和认可数量
depending on the number of atonements and approbations required.
如果评核超过四小时
If the review is to take longer than four hours,
将有午餐休息 会提前进行点餐
there will be a break for lunch, with the order taken in advance.
希望不会超过四小时
Well, I hope that won't be necessary.
这是午餐菜单
Here is the lunch menu.
我们先从好的说吧
Let's start with the positives.
你以优雅的态度接受了基尔的画
You received the gift of Kier paintings with grace.
你的考勤和尿检得分都属于极佳范围
Your attendance and urinalysis are both in the excellent range.
非常好
Wonderful.
但是 遗憾的是
Alternatively and sadly,
有三个匿名的举报
there have been three contentions reported anonymously
我们已作出调查和确认
which have been investigated and confirmed.
“第一个 使用过多大词”
"One: uses too many big words."
也许我在口头语方面应该运用...
Well, perchance I may colloquially employ a--
午餐休息后才是抗辩的时间
Anti-deflections will be heard after the lunch break.
好的 抱歉
Yes, sorry.
第二个 在你的多个工作日志中
Two: on several of your daily logs,
回形针别反了
the paper clip was installed back to front,
从而导致混乱 不知该从文件的哪一部分开始阅读
which led to a confusion as to where in the document to begin reading.
这些就是别错了的日志
Here are the incidents.
但我们今天的主要内容是以下
But the bulk of our day will revolve around the following.
你为马克S换了新的精检部团队
You brought in a new refining team for Mark S.
但团队未能和谐共事
which failed to coalesce.
你推出了善意改革
You instituted kindness reforms.
因为我不是哈蒙妮科贝尔
Because I'm not Harmony Cobel.
而善意改革似乎完全没有
Kindness reforms that seemed to have, in no way,
阻止团队回归后到处打探和游荡
deterred curiosity or idling by the team once they returned.
你安排了户外团建活动
You arranged an outdoor retreat and team-building occurrence
导致一名员工被解聘
which resulted in the termination of one employee,
并暴露了另一员工的真实身份
and the discovery of the true identity of another
这给伊根家族造成了极大的风险和损害
at great risk and harm to the Eagan name.
听着 塞斯 若马克斯科特完成冷港...
Look, Seth, Mark Scout's completion of Cold Harbor...
(冷港 完成进度:81%)
...这将载入史册
will be remembered
成为地球上最伟大的成就之一
as one of the greatest moments in the history of this planet.
它将在你的监管下发生
It will take place under your stewardship.
这会是你留给后世的惊人成就
That's quite a legacy you will leave.
谢谢 达蒙德先生
Thank you, Mr. Drummond.
这对我意义重大
That means a great deal.
(该进行表现评核了 塞斯米尔奇克)
这一里程碑事件似乎影响了你的判断力
This milestone seems to have clouded your judgment.
我认为是时候回到最根本的原则了 塞斯
I think it's time to go back to the basics, Seth.
记得那些分离员工在更大层面上的使命
To remember these severed workers' greater purpose...
并以他们真正的身份对待他们
and to treat them as what they really are.
(塞斯米尔奇克的成就和失败)
(塞斯米尔奇克的问题)
(使用过多大词 错误使用回形针)
(新精检团队未能持久 灾难性户外团建 失败)
(完成进度:85%)
我要加强监管了
I'm tightening the leash.
嗨 马克
Hi, Mark.
米尔奇克先生
Mr. Milchick.
你提前了六分钟下班
I see you left work six minutes early.
我可以进来吗
May I come in?
我走后 葬礼进行得怎么样
How was the rest of the funeral?
你们获得所需的东西了吗
Did you get what you needed from it?
是的
Yeah, sure.
嘿 黄小姐记笔记了吗
Hey, did Miss Huang take notes?
我等不及读她在你给我看的 那份报纸上发表的文章了
I can't wait to read her article about it in that newspaper you showed me.
那报纸叫什么来着
What was it called again?
《谎话连篇公报》
The Bullshit Gazette?
希望从现在起我们可以 放下这些哀悼和混乱
Hopefully, now we can put all this grief and tumult behind us
憧憬更有工作效率的未来
and look forward to some productive workdays ahead.
你是说把数字放进那个东西...
You mean putting the numbers in the thing--
- 精检 - 对
- Refining. - Right.
对 你觉得可以吗
Yes. Does that sound good?
听你的就好 米尔奇克先生
Whatever you say, Mr. Milchick.
赞美基尔
Praise Kier.
你和赫莉R聊过了吗
Did you and Helly R. catch up?
聊过了
We did.
你告诉她你和她外面的自己 在户外团建时上床了吗
Did you tell her that you fucked her outie at the ORTBO?
海伦娜伊根
Helena Eagan,
本公司领袖的继任者
leader-in-waiting of this company.
今晚好好休息
Have a restful evening.
“工人们兢兢业业
"The workers were diligent,
专注手头的工作
focused on the task at hand.
我惊喜地发现 没有任何员工戴着手表
Pleasantly surprised, I noticed that not a single worker had a watch.
他们只是会用门口的 一个巨大的标准时钟看时间
They simply referenced a large standard clock near the door,
这里只有指针 数字 齿轮和使命
just hands and numbers and cogs and purpose.
虽然墙上的时钟属于你最大的上司
Your sovereign boss may own the clock that greets you from the wall,
但你有幸听到时钟滴答作响 因此应该感到快乐”
but you get to enjoy its ticking and thus should be happy."
是
Yes.
宝贝 这和你之前表达的观点完全相反
Babe, it's the literal opposite of what you were saying before.
好的
Okay.
我明白你为什么会这么觉得
I see how you'd feel that way.
但娜塔指出的其中一点就是...
But one point that Nat made was--
“娜塔” 好吧
Nat, okay.
她说公司里的自己 在有框架的环境里发展得更好
She said that innies tend to thrive in an environment of structure,
建立框架后
and once that is established,
他们就能更自在地自我扩展
then they are more open to self-expansion.
所以我是想以他们的语言表达
So I am just trying to speak their language.
我知道 但这听起来像是卢蒙的语言
I know, but this sounds like Lumon's language.
这是特洛伊木马
Well, it's a Trojan's horse.
如果可以将我的理念 传递给世界各地的分离员工
If I can get my ideas to severed workers all across the world,
那也许能掀起革命
it might beget a revolution.
但这不是你的理念啊
But these aren't your ideas.
这不是你的理念 而且...
These are not your ideas, and also...
随便吧
Whatever.
而且什么
And what?
好吧 卢蒙伤害员工 你知道的 如果你想让自己的文字变得平淡
Okay, Lumon hurts people, you know that, and if you want to water down your work
被他们用来洗脑
so they can use it for their fucking propaganda,
那你也是在伤害那些员工
then you're hurting people too.
好吧 我会思考你的话的
Okay. I will reflect on your words.
谢谢
Thank you.
另外
And also,
这是一个经济和创意的机会
this is a fiscal and creative opportunity
是我之前从没遇到过的
unlike any I have yet seen.
我不太愿意就这样放弃它
And I'm not inclined to just walk away from it.
除非你觉得我的书卖出数百万本
Unless me selling millions of copies of my book
以及随之而来的富裕生活 对你来说没有吸引力
and the life that that manages to give us has somehow lost its appeal for you.
好吧 随便吧 我睡了
Okay. Whatever. I'm gonna go to bed.
不 宝贝
No. Babe.
不 谢谢
No, thank you.
(电话亭)
又是我
It's me again.
所以 他们炒了我
So, they fired me.
我觉得他们知道 我公司里的自己在策划什么
I think they knew what my innie was up to.
我希望你...
I'm telling you to--
我得挂了
I have to go.
嘿
Hey!
你 你为什么跟踪我
You. Why are you following me?
我有个习惯
I got this thing.
有人跑到我家 大声叫我的名字时 我总想知道为什么
When somebody shows up on my doorstep screaming my name, I wanna know why.
算是个怪癖吧
Call it a quirk.
你为卢蒙工作
You're with Lumon.
你那天晚上为什么去我家
Why were you at my house the other night?
我不知道
I don't know.
那人根本不是你 对吗
It wasn't you at all, was it?
你是分离员工
You're severed.
我几周前被炒了
I got canned a couple of weeks ago.
我要求他们提供原因时
When I pressed them for a reason,
他们说 我公司里的自己 和另一个员工有违规的情感关系
they said my innie had an unsanctioned, erotic entanglement with another worker.
他们不愿说是谁
They wouldn't tell me who.
然后 你出现在我家门口
Then you show up at my door.
你觉得我们曾交往
You think we were an item?
菲尔德斯显然这么认为
Well, Fields certainly thinks so.
我们不得不取消了密尔沃基之旅 都是因为那件事
We had to cancel our trip to Milwaukee. Thanks for that.
- 菲尔德斯  - 我的丈夫 菲尔德斯
- Fields? - That's my husband, Fields.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
是 这...
Yeah, well...
很抱歉我刚才吼你
And I'm sorry I came at you just now.
没关系
It's fine.
也许你可以...我不知道
Maybe you could-- I don't know.
什么
What?
我们家有火腿 打算明天吃的
We got a ham. We're planning to have it tomorrow.
欢迎你来做客 我们可以坐下 好好聊
Might be nice if you come over. We could sit down, talk through it all.
你 我 还有...
You, me, and...
菲尔德斯
Fields.
可以
I suppose.
太好了
Great.
我们喜欢红酒
We like red wine.
昂贵
Expensive.
好的 明天
Okay. Tomorrow.
要载你一程吗
You need a lift?
我走路就好 谢谢
I'll walk. Thanks.
你肯定
You sure?
我知道你住在哪里
I know where you live.
- 明天见 - 好
- See you tomorrow. - Yes.
抱歉 没有蛋酒
Sorry there wasn't any eggnog.
可能过季了
Might be out of season.
你在搞什么
What the fuck are you doing?
我需要一些压力点 用来激活你的记忆
I needed some pressure points. Things to rattle your memories.
- 针织  - 是
- Knitting? - Yeah.
她说这让她空出脑子思考
She said it gave her time to think.
(快件 骨灰)
那是她吗
That her?
我以为是她
What I thought was her.
她没死 只是不在这里
She's not dead. She's just not here.
那里面是谁
Who's in there?
他们在停尸房有熟人
They know people at the morgue.
是他们的员工 就像基尔一贯的作风
On the payroll, like everywhere else in Kier.
你还好吧
You feel all right?
算是吧 那么 我们是要...
Basically. So, are we gonna...
再等一天
One more day.
通常那是最佳时间
Usually that's best.
通常 你只做过一次
Usually? You've done this once.
我不想太仓促
I don't wanna rush things.
有风险
There's risk.
这不是精确的科学 马克
It's not an exact science, Mark.
我都不确定这算是科学 不过 好吧
I'm not sure it's science, period, but okay.
零食还够吗
You good on snacks?
暂时还够
For now.
他们在伤害她吗
Are they hurting her?
我不知道
I don't know.
你外面的自己
Your outie.
什么
What?
我什么都没说
I didn't say anything.
你外面的自己可以在20秒内完成侧方停车
Your outie can parallel park in less than 20 seconds.
你外面的自己溜滑轮技术很棒
Your outie can roller-skate with grace.
你外面的自己在三个营业日内 支付所有瓦斯和电费账单
Your outie pays all of his gas and electric bills within three business days.
你外面的自己刮胡须时 听音乐 但洗澡时不听
Your outie listens to music while shaving, but not while showering.
你外面的自己喜欢点双球冰淇淋
Your outie prefers two scoops of ice cream in a serving,
但必须是同一种口味
but they must be the same flavor.
你外面的自己曾经捉到一只蝴蝶
Your outie once captured a butterfly.
你外面的自己将要...
Your outie is going to--